{
    "id": "20cca5cc6f354d8ebf0fbc8858aedee5",
    "title": "Sentence Completion Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I ..................... her since the day before yesterday",
            "description": "The present perfect is more common with the time expressions for and since.",
            "answers": [
                "didn't see",
                "haven't seen",
                "hadn't seen"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Professionals ..................... nurses and teachers are often underpaid.",
            "description": "Either such as or like is possible here. Such as is more formal. ",
            "answers": [
                "such like",
                "as",
                "such as",
                "like"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The girl ....................... sits next to Sam is his niece.",
            "description": "Use who to refer to people use which to refer to things. ",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "whom",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "You …………………………….. do something to improve the situation.",
            "description": "Either should or ought to is possible here. ",
            "answers": [
                "ought to",
                "ought",
                "should"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "You ......................... permit this.",
            "description": "Must is a modal auxiliary. Questions and negatives are made without do.",
            "answers": [
                "must not",
                "must don't",
                "don't must"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I opened the door but …………………... was there.",
            "description": "Not anybody means the same as nobody.",
            "answers": [
                "anybody",
                "nobody"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "This is the sixth time you …………………………….. the same question.",
            "description": "The present perfect is common after this is the first/second/last etc. ",
            "answers": [
                "asked",
                "have asked",
                "had asked"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He was a ……………………………. child who rarely spoke to anyone.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "quite",
                "quiet"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She is the ……………………………. girl in the class.",
            "description": "Chirpiest is the superlative form of chirpy.",
            "answers": [
                "most chirpy",
                "chirpiest",
                "most chirpiest"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I failed the test …………………………….. I hadn’t prepared well.",
            "description": "Because is a conjunction because of is a preposition. ",
            "answers": [
                "because",
                "because of"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I worked ………………………. the best of my ability.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "to",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He assaulted his brother …………………………… he was jealous of him.",
            "description": "Because is a conjunction. ",
            "answers": [
                "because",
                "because of"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}